ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pittsburgh, Scranton & Wilkes-Barre, and West Virginia Regional Joint Board and Main Pants & Clothing Corp., 1976- 1982 (Box 185, Folder 7)
- New England Regional Joint Board and M & M Pant Co., Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 185, Folder 8)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and Main Pants & Clothing Corp., 1955-1975 (Box 185, Folder 9)
- New England, Local #377 and Made well Manufacturing, 1939-1985 (Box 185, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Madame Renee Laundry, 1975 (Box 185, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Madame Liorets Laundry, 1975 (Box 185, Folder 12)
- New York Joint Board and M & S Leather, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 185, Folder 13)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Sharpe Manufacturing Co., 1976-1983 (Box 185, Folder 14)
- New York Joint Board and Shearling-N-Things, Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 185, Folder 15)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Sharp Bros., Inc., 1966-1979 (Box 185, Folder 16)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Sellersville Manufacturing Co., 1982 (Box 185, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board, Cutters' Local #4, List of Companies, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Washable Clothing, Sportswear, and Allied Industries Retirement Fund and Amalgamated Life Insurance Co., Inc., 1953-1979 (Box 186, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Labor Standards Association, 1960 (Box 186, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board, Outerwear Agreements, Company List, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 4)
- New York, Bushelmen's Agreements, Company List (Box 186, Folder 5)
- Local #340, Retail Stores, Company List, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 6)
- Washable Clothing, Sportswear & Novelty Workers, Local #129, Company List, 1962 (Box 186, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries, Company List, 1978-1980 (Box 186, Folder 8)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Shirt, Robe, and Leisurewear Apparel Association of America, Inc., 1966- 1975 (Box 186, Folder 9)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Men's and Boys' Shirt and Leisurewear Association, Inc., 1966-1975 (Box 186, Folder 10)
- Textile Workers Union of America, Founding Agreements, 1935-1954 (Box 186, Folder 11)
- ACWA Affiliates, Apparel Plant Information, 1975 (Box 186, Folder 12)
- ACWA Affiliates, Bushelmen's Survey Forms, 1981-1985 (Box 186, Folder 13)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and multi-employer bargaining group, 1972-1975 (Box 186, Folder 14)
- ACWA Affiliates, Bushelmen's Survey Average, 1983 (Box 186, Folder 15)
- Journeymen Tailors Unions, Bushelmen's Agreements, Company Lists, 1971-1975 (Box 186, Folder 16)
- ACWA Affiliates, Bushelmen's Scale of Wages, 1964-1967 (Box 186, Folder 17)
- ACWA Affiliates, Bushelmen's Agreements, Company List and Information, 1968-1977 (Box 186, Folder 18)
- ACWA Affiliates, Bushelmen's Settlements by Joint Board, 1980-1981 (Box 186, Folder 19)
- ACWA Affiliates, Bushelmen's Agreements, Fringe Benefit Provisions, 1980-1981 (Box 186, Folder 20)
- ACWA Affiliates, Bushelmen's Agreements, Fringe Benefits and Wage Provisions, 1975-1976 (Box 186, Folder 21)
- Import Agreements, 1978-1986 (Box 186, Folder 22)
- New York Joint Board and Manhattan Merchant Tailors' Association, 1963-1977 (Box 186, Folder 23)
- New York Joint Board and Merchant Tailors' Society of the City of New York, Inc., 1963-1975 (Box 186, Folder 24)
- New York Joint Board and Merchant Tailors Institute, 1963 (Box 186, Folder 25)
- New York Joint Board and New York Clothing Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1957-1971 (Box 186, Folder 26)
- New York Joint Board and Retail Apparel Merchants Association, Inc., 1969-1978 (Box 186, Folder 27)
- New York Joint Board, Bushelmen's Agreements and Retail Apparel Merchants Association, Inc., 1958-1978 (Box 186, Folder 28)
- Retail Clothing Salesmen's Union, Local #340 and Retail Apparel Merchants Association, Inc., 1966-1979 (Box 186, Folder 29)
- Journeymen Tailors' Union, Local #115 and Merchant Tailors' Society of New Haven, CT, 1960-1980 (Box 186, Folder 30)
- New York Joint Board, Market Agreements, 1939-1971 (Box 186, Folder 31)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Minnesota Apparel Industries, 1946-1969 (Box 186, Folder 32)
- Los Angeles Joint Board and Pacific Coast Garment Manufacturers, 1960 (Box 186, Folder 33)
- New York Joint Board and Uniform Manufacturers' Exchange, Inc., 1963-1977 (Box 186, Folder 34)
- New York Joint Board and Retail Merchants Association, Company List, 1975-1978 (Box 186, Folder 35)
- New York Joint Board and Brooklyn Merchant Tailors' Association, 1963 (Box 186, Folder 36)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board, Standard Contract, 1982 (Box 186, Folder 37)
- Local #1733 and #1932, Silk & Rayon Dyers and Printers Association, 1993-1995 (Box 186, Folder 38)
- Federation of Dyers, Finishers, Printers and Bleachers of America, 1933-1950 (Box 187, Folder 1)
- Dye and Machine Print Contracts, 1951-1961 (Box 187, Folder 2)
- Dye and Machine Print Contracts, 1963-1974 (Box 187, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries, Laundry Workers Joint Board, Cleaners and Dyers Union, 1941-1978 (Box 187, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries, 1969-1978 (Box 187, Folder 5)
- Tannery and Leather Workers' Union, Local #1712 and Tanners Association of Fulton County, Inc., 1960-1986 (Box 187, Folder 6)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and U.S. Fabric Glove Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1966-1972 (Box 187, Folder 7)
- Washable Clothing, Sportswear & Novelty Workers, Local #169 and Uniform Manufacturers Exchange, Inc., 1977 (Box 187, Folder 8)
- South Jersey Joint Board and South Jersey Mens Manufacturers & Contractors Association, 1980 (Box 187, Folder 9)
- National Association of Glove Manufacturers, 1977 (Box 187, Folder 10)
- Washable Clothing, Sportswear & Novelty Workers, Local #169 and Washable Suits, Novelties & Sportswear Contractors' Association, Inc., 1969-1987 (Box 187, Folder 11)
- Washable Clothing, Sportswear & Novelty Workers, Local #169, Independent Contracts, 1969-1975 (Box 187, Folder 12)
- New York Joint Board of Neckwear Workers, Local #250C and #253C, Standard Contract, 1982-1990 (Box 187, Folder 13)
- New York Joint Board of Neckwear Workers, Local #250 and #253 and Men's Neckwear Manufacturers Association of New York, Inc., 1964-1976 (Box 187, Folder 14)
- New York Joint Board of Neckwear Workers, Local #250 and #253 and Independent Contractors, 1964 (Box 187, Folder 15)
- Laundry Workers Joint Board and Sullivan County Laundry Owners, 1963-1976 (Box 187, Folder 16)
- United Custom Tailors and Uniform Contractors Association, Inc., Company List, 1962 (Box 187, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and Greater Clothing Contractors Association, Company List, 1968-1980 (Box 187, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries, Handbook, 1975 (Box 187, Folder 19)
- Laundry Workers Joint Board, Contract Supplements, 1967-1971 (Box 187, Folder 20)
- Journeymen Tailors' Union, Local #71 and Seattle Retail Clothiers Association, 1966-1969 (Box 187, Folder 21)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, Standard Contracts, 1969-1973 (Box 187, Folder 22)
- Northern California Joint Board and San Francisco Retailers Council, 1967 (Box 187, Folder 23)
- Minnesota Joint Board, Supplemental Association Agreements, 1959-1970 (Box 187, Folder 24)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board, 1935-1963 (Box 187, Folder 25)
- Boston Joint Board, 1917-1963 (Box 187, Folder 26)
- Wholesale Clothiers' Association of Chicago, 1934-1937 (Box 187, Folder 27)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, Manufacturers' Association, 1917-1963 (Box 187, Folder 28)
- Rochester Joint Board and the Clothiers Exchange of Rochester, 1919-1937 (Box 187, Folder 29)
- Cincinnati, Standard Agreement, 1937 (Box 187, Folder 30)
- Montreal Joint Board, Standard Agreements, 1917-1961 (Box 187, Folder 31)
- New York Joint Board, Standard Agreements, 1921-1965 (Box 187, Folder 32)